[
    {"prompt":"a", "answer": "ア"},
    {"prompt":"i", "answer": "イ"},
    {"prompt":"u", "answer": "ウ"},
    {"prompt":"e", "answer": "エ"},
    {"prompt":"o", "answer": "オ"},
    {"prompt":"ya", "answer": "ャ"},
    {"prompt":"yu", "answer": "ュ"},
    {"prompt":"yo", "answer": "ョ"},
    {"prompt":"ka", "answer": "カ"},
    {"prompt":"ki", "answer": "キ"},
    {"prompt":"ku", "answer": "ク"},
    {"prompt":"ke", "answer": "ケ"},
    {"prompt":"ko", "answer": "コ"},
    {"prompt":"kya", "answer": "キャ"},
    {"prompt":"kyu", "answer": "キュ"},
    {"prompt":"kyo", "answer": "キョ"},
    {"prompt":"sa", "answer": "サ"},
    {"prompt":"shi", "answer": "シ"},
    {"prompt":"su", "answer": "ス"},
    {"prompt":"se", "answer": "セ"},
    {"prompt":"so", "answer": "ソ"},
    {"prompt":"sha", "answer": "シャ"},
    {"prompt":"shu", "answer": "シュ"},
    {"prompt":"sho", "answer": "ショ"},
    {"prompt":"ta", "answer": "タ"},
    {"prompt":"chi", "answer": "チ"},
    {"prompt":"tsu", "answer": "ツ"},
    {"prompt":"te", "answer": "テ"},
    {"prompt":"to", "answer": "ト"},
    {"prompt":"cha", "answer": "チャ"},
    {"prompt":"chu", "answer": "チュ"},
    {"prompt":"cho", "answer": "チョ"},
    {"prompt":"na", "answer": "ナ"},
    {"prompt":"ni", "answer": "ニ"},
    {"prompt":"nu", "answer": "ヌ"},
    {"prompt":"ne", "answer": "ネ"},
    {"prompt":"no", "answer": "ノ"},
    {"prompt":"nya", "answer": "ニャ"},
    {"prompt":"nyu", "answer": "ニュ"},
    {"prompt":"nyo", "answer": "ニョ"},
    {"prompt":"ha", "answer": "ハ"},
    {"prompt":"hi", "answer": "ヒ"},
    {"prompt":"fu", "answer": "フ"},
    {"prompt":"he", "answer": "ヘ"},
    {"prompt":"ho", "answer": "ホ"},
    {"prompt":"hya", "answer": "ヒャ"},
    {"prompt":"hyu", "answer": "ヒュ"},
    {"prompt":"hyo", "answer": "ヒョ"},
    {"prompt":"ma", "answer": "マ"},
    {"prompt":"mi", "answer": "ミ"},
    {"prompt":"mu", "answer": "ム"},
    {"prompt":"me", "answer": "メ"},
    {"prompt":"mo", "answer": "モ"},
    {"prompt":"mya", "answer": "ミャ"},
    {"prompt":"myu", "answer": "ミュ"},
    {"prompt":"myo", "answer": "ミョ"},
    {"prompt":"ya", "answer": "ヤ"},
    {"prompt":"yu", "answer": "ユ"},
    {"prompt":"yo", "answer": "ヨ"},
    {"prompt":"ra", "answer": "ラ"},
    {"prompt":"ri", "answer": "リ"},
    {"prompt":"ru", "answer": "ル"},
    {"prompt":"re", "answer": "レ"},
    {"prompt":"ro", "answer": "ロ"},
    {"prompt":"rya", "answer": "リャ"},
    {"prompt":"ryu", "answer": "リュ"},
    {"prompt":"ryo", "answer": "リョ"},
    {"prompt":"wa", "answer": "ワ"},
    {"prompt":"n", "answer": "ン"},
    {"prompt":"ga", "answer": "ガ"},
    {"prompt":"gi", "answer": "ギ"},
    {"prompt":"gu", "answer": "グ"},
    {"prompt":"ge", "answer": "ゲ"},
    {"prompt":"go", "answer": "ゴ"},
    {"prompt":"gya", "answer": "ギャ"},
    {"prompt":"gyu", "answer": "ギュ"},
    {"prompt":"gyo", "answer": "ギョ"},
    {"prompt":"za", "answer": "ザ"},
    {"prompt":"ji", "answer": "ジ"},
    {"prompt":"zu", "answer": "ズ"},
    {"prompt":"ze", "answer": "ゼ"},
    {"prompt":"zo", "answer": "ゾ"},
    {"prompt":"ja", "answer": "ジャ"},
    {"prompt":"ju", "answer": "ジュ"},
    {"prompt":"jo", "answer": "ジョ"},
    {"prompt":"da", "answer": "ダ"},
    {"prompt":"ji", "answer": "ヂ"},
    {"prompt":"zu", "answer": "ヅ"},
    {"prompt":"de", "answer": "デ"},
    {"prompt":"do", "answer": "ド"},
    {"prompt":"ja", "answer": "ヂャ"},
    {"prompt":"ju", "answer": "ヂュ"},
    {"prompt":"jo", "answer": "ヂョ"},
    {"prompt":"ba", "answer": "バ"},
    {"prompt":"bi", "answer": "ビ"},
    {"prompt":"bu", "answer": "ブ"},
    {"prompt":"be", "answer": "ベ"},
    {"prompt":"bo", "answer": "ボ"},
    {"prompt":"bya", "answer": "ビャ"},
    {"prompt":"byu", "answer": "ビュ"},
    {"prompt":"byo", "answer": "ビョ"},
    {"prompt":"pa", "answer": "パ"},
    {"prompt":"pi", "answer": "ピ"},
    {"prompt":"pu", "answer": "プ"},
    {"prompt":"pe", "answer": "ペ"},
    {"prompt":"po", "answer": "ポ"},
    {"prompt":"pya", "answer": "ピャ"},
    {"prompt":"pyu", "answer": "ピュ"},
    {"prompt":"pyo", "answer": "ピョ"}
]
